butapips.com 2013-06-26

# Privacy Policy | BUTAPIPS

_Security and Disclosure_

butapips.com respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients as well as our current clients.

_Personal Information_

When you apply for or maintain a live account with butapips.com, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. Such information may include:

Name

Email Address

Phone Number

Physical Address

Trading/Risk Capital

The broker you are using

_About Cookies_

Cookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. butapips.com may set and access butapips.com cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. butapips.com or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with butapips.com's products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable.

_Security Technology_

butapips.com uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than butapips.com while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our Web sites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data.

_Sharing Information With Third Parties_

butapips.com does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with butapips.com, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to butapips.com. Non-affiliated companies that assist butapips.com in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that butapips.com dictates.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your expressed consent.

We want you to know that butapips.com will not sell your personal information.

_Regulatory Disclosure_

Under limited circumstances, butapips.com may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission.

_Opt Out_

You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request; however, failure to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete, and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.

If you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to our affiliates or other third parties as described in this Policy, please contact us via e-mail at: info@butapips.com
